<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>www.samachar4media.com (Fullstory)</title>
    <description>Media News, Advertising News, Media Industry Updates – Samachar4media</description>
    <language>hi</language>
    <copyright>Copyright @ 2008 samachar4media Media Private Limited. All rights reserved</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://storage.googleapis.com/media-news/rss/49593.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
      <title>FICCI के सम्मेलन में उदय शंकर ने दिया बड़ा बयान, जताई ये उम्मीद</title>
      <author>S4M Online Bureau</author>
      <pubDate>12/03/2019</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&amp;lsquo;भारतीय वाणिज्य एवं उद्योग महासंघ&amp;rsquo; (FICCI) फ्रेम्स के 20वें एडिशन की शुरुआत काफी धूमधाम से हुई। तीन दिवसीय इस वैश्विक सम्मेलन में पूरे मीडिया और एंटरटेनमेंट सेक्टर जैसे-फिल्म्स, ब्रॉडकास्ट (टीवी और रेडियो), प्रिंट मीडिया, डिजिटल एंटरटेनमेंट, एडवर्टाइजमेंट आदि से जुड़े दिग्गज शामिल हुए।&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;सम्मेलन के उद्घाटन समारोह में &amp;lsquo;फिक्की&amp;rsquo; के वाइस प्रेजिडेंट उदय शंकर ने कहा, &amp;lsquo;यह काफी गौरवशाली और भावुक पल है, क्योंकि फिक्की फ्रेम्स अपनी 20वीं वर्षगांठ मना रहा है। करीब 20 साल पहले जब कुछ दूरदर्शी लोगों ने मीडिया और एंटरटेनमेंट कम्युनिटी के लिए इस तरह का प्लेटफॉर्म तैयार करने का फैसला लिया था, तब न तो भारतीय मीडिया और न ही फ्रेम्स आज जैसी स्थिति में था। ये 20 साल दोनों के लिए काफी उतार-चढ़ाव वाले रहे हैं।&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;उन्होंने कहा, &amp;rsquo;20 साल पहले के मुकाबले मीडिया और एंटरटेनमेंट इंडस्ट्री आज काफी आगे बढ़ चुकी है और फिक्की फ्रेम्स को उस समय ऐसे प्लेटफॉर्म के रूप में तैयार किया गया था, जहां पर मीडिया और एंटरटेनमेंट कम्युनिटी आपस में बैठकर विभिन्न मुद्दों पर चर्चा कर सके, लेकिन आज यह काफी विस्तार कर चुका है। आज के समय में मीडिया और एंटरटेनमेंट इंडस्ट्री रोजगार, संपत्ति और स्वास्थ्य जैसे राष्ट्रीय सपनों को पूरा करने के लिए सक्रिय भूमिका निभाने के लिए तैयार है और यह आने वाले समय में न्यू इंडिया में अपनी अहम भूमिका निभा सकता है।&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;कार्यक्रम के बारे में पूरी रिपोर्ट आप यहां देख सकते हैं-&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;The 20th Edition of FICCI Frames is a three day global convention covering the entire gamut of Media &amp;amp; Entertainment like Films, Broadcast (TV &amp;amp; Radio), Print Media, Digital Entertainment, Advertisement, Live Entertainment Events, Digital &amp;amp; New Media, Animation, Gaming, Visual Effects, etc. It is attended by nearly 2000 Indian and 800 foreign delegates encompassing the entire universe of media and entertainment. It attracts not only the industry stakeholders from across the world, but also the government policy makers from India and abroad.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;Here are the opening remarks by Uday Shankar, Vice President, FICCI at 20 years of FICCI Frames:&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&amp;ldquo;Welcome to FICCI Frames 2019. It is a proud and an emotional moment because this is the 20th anniversary of Frames. Two decades ago when some visionaries decided to create this platform for the media &amp;amp; entertainment community, neither the Indian media nor Frames was what it is today. These 20 years have been a spectacular roller coaster ride for both. From being a very small and somewhat fragile media &amp;amp; entertainment industry 20 years ago, today it is a source of global ambition and envy and so is FICCI Frames. Frames was envisioned to be a platform where the media &amp;amp; entertainment community could get together to discuss its issues. Given the scale at which it is today, it would do its visionary founders very proud. Over time, Frames has become the most meaningful platform for media &amp;amp; entertainment community in this part of the world. Attempts to clone it can at best be described as unrealised ambitions. My heartiest congratulations to FICCI and team Frames, led by Leena Jaisani, who have been relentless in their passion and their commitment. This would not have been possible without all of you. On behalf of the entire media &amp;amp; entertainment community, I salute you all.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;The transformation in the media &amp;amp; entertainment industry in India in the last 20 years has been mind boggling to say the least. It is one of the major media markets in the world now. It is also one of the most exciting media markets anywhere in the world with every major global company trying to give shape to its ambition in India, and with the Indian companies challenging them very vigorously.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;So what does the journey ahead look like? We will hear the views of accomplished experts and practitioners over the next three days. But in my humble opinion, the great Indian media &amp;amp; entertainment story has just begun. We are standing at an inflexion point. We can either sit on our laurels or we can use the winds of change to fill our sails and embark on an even more exciting and glorious journey. We need to recognise the power of this creative sector in helping realise the national aspirations. Indian media &amp;amp; entertainment industry is ready to contribute more actively and more substantially than probably any other sector to the national dream of creating jobs, assets and wealth. What&amp;rsquo;s more is that we are also in a position to be the flag bearers of a brand new India all over the world. We are already seeing the innovations that are taking place in this country in the domain of Sports, or in Digital, where Indian creativity is being talked about globally and attracting the interest of one and all. However, we need to make sure that our policies are aligned to accelerate creativity and growth. Wherever we find drags, we should be able to step in and align them while making sure that the larger social interest is always at the front and center. At the same time, we also need to make sure that in the name of social or national interest we do not waste the potential of this industry. That would not just be a disappointment but also very unfair to the world of good that this industry can do to the crores of people of this country who can benefit directly from it.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;I shall stop dwelling further on this subject because that is what you are going to hear from a series of illustrious speakers over the next three days. Before finishing, I would just like to highlight that this has been a very successful year for the FICCI media &amp;amp; entertainment committee. The committee has been instrumental in bringing about some key reforms for the industry, including a downward revision in the GST slab for entertainment services and the tabling of the anti cam-cording provisions under the Cinematograph Act. It marks a very satisfying year for me as the Chairman of the committee and I would like to congratulate all those who have been involved.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;With this I would like to call upon Charles Rivkin, the Chairman &amp;amp; CEO of Motion Pictures Association of America, to deliver the industry address.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <storyimages>https://storage.googleapis.com/media-news/49593-uday.jpg</storyimages>
      <guid>49593</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
